<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[wideas]]></title>
  <link href="http://wuyb.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://wuyb.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-06T23:31:31+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://wuyb.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Yanbo Wu]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[life.alloc.init]]></title>
    <link href="http://wuyb.github.com/blog/2013/03/20/life-alloc-init/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-20T03:57:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://wuyb.github.com/blog/2013/03/20/life-alloc-init</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It has been more than 16 months since I came back to Beijing - the city that I lived, loved and left. Things haven&#8217;t changed a lot, except myself. I got my PhD degree, finally, after three-and-a-half-year i-don&#8217;t-know-what-i-was-doing time. Like a trophy, it looks good on the wall and in the resume, but deep down in my heart, I know it is somewhat a waste of time and energy. I had too many ideas to change the world, or at least to improve people&#8217;s life in some way. It just passed by because &#8216;I do not have the time because I am a PhD student.&#8217;.</p>

<p>Now I have been back and spent 16 months in trivial and less meaningful things, such as Hukou and immigration application. Life has confused me once again. Is the life now what I want? The answer is absolutely no. What is that I really want? I can&#8217;t answer definitely. I know, however, I need to do something, make something and realize some of my earlier dreams. Hence, a new project is started.</p>

<p>It is still too early to publish it (I know &#8220;lean startup&#8221;&#8230;) but I have a prototype running. It is never late to learn so design driven development has become my new topic. I love neat designs: the iPhone, Macbook Air etc. I don&#8217;t know how many readers I will have, but just in case you are one of them and are interested, drop me a line (found my email <a href="http://wuyb.com/" title="wuyb.com">here</a>) please.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
